[
  {
    "task_id": 1,
    "question": "текст номер 1",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "task_id": 2,
    "question": "текст номер 2",
    "answer": 20
  },
  {
    "task_id": 3,
    "question": "текст номер 3",
    "answer": 30
  },
  {
    "task_id": 4,
    "question": "текст номер 4",
    "answer": 40
  },
  {
    "task_id": 5,
    "question": "текст номер 5",
    "answer": 50
  },
  {
    "task_id": 6,
    "question": "текст номер 6",
    "answer": 60
  },
  {
    "task_id": 7,
    "question": "текст номер 7",
    "answer": 70
  },
  {
    "task_id": 8,
    "question": "текст номер 8",
    "answer": 80
  },
  {
    "task_id": 9,
    "question": "текст номер 9",
    "answer": 90
  },
  {
    "task_id": 10,
    "question": "текст номер 10",
    "answer": 100
  },
  {
    "task_id": 11,
    "question": "текст номер 11",
    "answer": 110
  },
  {
    "task_id": 12,
    "question": "текст номер 12",
    "answer": 120
  },
  {
    "task_id": 13,
    "question": "текст номер 13",
    "answer": 130
  },
  {
    "task_id": 14,
    "question": "текст номер 14",
    "answer": 140
  },
  {
    "task_id": 15,
    "question": "текст номер 15",
    "answer": 150
  },
  {
    "task_id": 16,
    "question": "текст номер 16",
    "answer": 160
  },
  {
    "task_id": 17,
    "question": "текст номер 17",
    "answer": 170
  },
  {
    "task_id": 18,
    "question": "текст номер 18",
    "answer": 180
  },
  {
    "task_id": 19,
    "question": "текст номер 19",
    "answer": 190
  },
  {
    "task_id": 20,
    "question": "текст номер 20",
    "answer": 200
  },
  {
    "task_id": 21,
    "question": "текст номер 21",
    "answer": 210
  },
  {
    "task_id": 22,
    "question": "текст номер 22",
    "answer": 220
  },
  {
    "task_id": 23,
    "question": "текст номер 23",
    "answer": 230
  },
  {
    "task_id": 24,
    "question": "текст номер 24",
    "answer": 240
  },
  {
    "task_id": 25,
    "question": "текст номер 25",
    "answer": 250
  },
  {
    "task_id": 26,
    "question": "текст номер 26",
    "answer": 260
  },
  {
    "task_id": 27,
    "question": "текст номер 27",
    "answer": 270
  },
  {
    "task_id": 28,
    "question": "текст номер 28",
    "answer": 280
  },
  {
    "task_id": 29,
    "question": "текст номер 29",
    "answer": 290
  },
  {
    "task_id": 30,
    "question": "текст номер 30",
    "answer": 300
  },
  {
    "task_id": 31,
    "question": "текст номер 31",
    "answer": 310
  },
  {
    "task_id": 32,
    "question": "текст номер 32",
    "answer": 320
  }
]